本字幕由YYeTs字幕組原創翻譯
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息
饑餓
的青春
第二季  第七集
那是什么氣味  今天是垃圾日嗎
What's that smell? Is it garbage day?
不  我做了早餐
No, I made breakfast.
用垃圾做的嗎
Did you make it with garbage?
自從你媽媽去世后
Since your mom passed away,
我知道她生日時你會很難過
I know how hard it is for you on her birthday,
所以我給你做了雞蛋  培根和酪乳煎餅
So I made you a feast of eggs, bacon and buttermilk pancakes!
太貼心了
That is so sweet.
那些東西在哪兒啊
Where are those things?
而且我放了二十塊
Also, I put $20
到史密森尼博物館茱莉亞·蔡爾德旅行罐里
in the Julia Child Smithsonian trip jar
如果有人不再從罐子里偷硬幣
and if someone would stop taking quarters out of the jar,
我們就終于能去你和你媽媽
we would finally be able to take that trip
夢寐以求的旅行了
you and your mom always dreamed about.
聽到了嗎
You hear that?
媽媽說你是最棒的閨蜜
Mom just said you're the best friend ever.
謝謝  戴蒙德太太
Thank you, Mrs. Diamond.
你說什么
What was that now?
早餐應該是一天中最重要的一餐
Breakfast should be your most important meal of the day,
不是最不重要的
not your last.
我覺得她很聰明
I think she's a smart lady.
-我來給你做早餐吧  -好主意
- Why don't I make you breakfast? - Oh, good idea.
兩個有機雞蛋  烤面包  培根煎脆一點
Two organic eggs, toast, bacon extra crispy,
快點  因為我要去上班了
and tick-tock, 'cause I gotta get to work.
翻譯   冰藍   aaaBao   胖兔純   roaddog
校對  roaddog
時間軸  aaaBao   吉吉
后期  斯人   總監  roaddog
加比  再來點咖啡
Gabi! More coffee!
我兩天沒睡了
I haven't slept in two days.
看來某人很走運啊
Sounds like somebody's getting lucky.
真是骯臟人做骯臟事啊
That puts the "nasty" in "doing the nasty."
和埃蘭的性愛很狂野
Sex with Alan is wild.
我感覺自己是叢林女王艾略特
I feel like Elliot, Queen of the Jungle.
昨晚我們在一個特別瘋狂的地方做了
Last night we did it in the craziest place...
臥室地板上
the bedroom floor.
拜托  我在衛浴寢具批發商城的
Oh please, I've done it on the floor
地板上做過
of Bed, Bath & Beyond.
我帶著八折優惠券進去
I went in with a 20% off coupon,
結果他們免單了
and got 100% off.
話說...
So...
在我超棒的女朋友下來之前  我需要你的幫助
Before my amazing girlfriend comes down, I need your help.
舊金山記者協會
Shauna is being honored
要給肖娜頒獎
by the San Francisco Journalists Association,
我得想出一個超棒的禮物
and I need to think of an awesome gift.
還有
Oh, and...
摩天輪
ferris wheel.
瞧瞧我
Oh, look at me.
哥有錢  買得起摩天輪
I'm rich. I can buy a ferris wheel.
我是說我最瘋狂的做愛地點
I was talking about the craziest place I ever had sex.
在摩天輪上
In a ferris wheel
婚禮現場  是嘉年華主題
at a wedding with a carnival theme.
誰有我牛
Beat that.
我有
I can.
我女兒七歲生日時
My daughter's seventh birthday
在充氣城堡里
in the bouncy castle
和小丑來了一發
with the clown.
原來小丑們
It turns out noses aren't
喜歡捏的不只是鼻子
the only thing clowns like to honk.
孩子  小丑  異性性行為
Kids, clowns, hetero sex--
這里沒我事了
there's nothing for me here.
除了布雷特...你還有個孩子嗎
You have another kid... besides Brett?
是啊  丹妮爾  她25歲了
Yeah, Danielle, she's 25.
兩個孩子
Two kids.
沒別的了吧
Is that it?
我不常說起丹妮爾
I don't talk about Danielle that often.
不幸的是  我們很多年沒說過話了
Unfortunately, we haven't spoken in years.
什么  母女不睦嗎  出了什么事
What? A mother-daughter not close? What happened?
加比  這聽起來像是私事
Gabi, sounds like it's kind of a private thing.
是啊  所以我才問
Yeah, yeah, that's why I'm asking.
沒事  喬什
It's okay, Josh.
我懷她是自己也是個孩子
I was a child myself when I had her.
要是說實話  我覺得我們太像了
And if I'm truthful, I think we're just too much alike.
現在我們可以說說早餐了嗎
Now can we talk about breakfast?
是的  你想吃蛋嗎
Yes. Would you like eggs?
你們互相發圣誕卡片嗎
And do you at least send each other Christmas cards?
我發的  但她沒有回過我
Well, I do. I just-- I never get one back.
電子賀卡都沒嗎
Not even an E-card?
那是免費的呀
But they're free.
最近一次的消息
Last I heard,
是她在佛蒙特州做手工楓糖漿
she was making artisanal maple syrup in Vermont.
我先失陪了  要去車里哭了
Now if you'll excuse me, I'm off to go cry in my car.
-肖娜  -我開玩笑的  有司機來接我
- Shauna! - I'm just kidding. A driver's picking me up.
我要去他的車里哭
I'm gonna cry in his car.
你知道給肖娜什么禮物好嗎
Hey, you know what a great gift for Shauna would be?
心理醫生  多謝了你
A therapist... thanks to you.
不  讓她和她女兒團聚
No. Get her and her daughter back together.
不  那是肖娜的私事
No, that's Shauna's personal business.
-我不該插手  -是啊  所以
- It's not my place to get involved. - Yeah, that's why
這會是個很棒的驚喜  她不會料到的
it would be such a great surprise-- she'd never see it coming.
每個母親和女兒都想親密
Every mother and daughter want to be close.
拜托  喬什  相信我
Come on, Josh, trust me.
相信你嗎  不
Trust you? No.
-但是  -不
- But-- - No!
-那是堅定的...  -是的
- Is that a firm-- - Yes!
-你同意了  -不
- So that's a yes! - No!
不行
No!
No.
-就...  -不行
- Just-- - No.
好吧
Okay.
我的媽呀
Oh my damn.
毯子下面藏著頭豬
A pig in a blanket.
"毯包豬"在美國指香腸面包
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know what happened.
我進來拿喬什要送去干洗的西裝
I came to get Josh's tux for the cleaner's,
聞到了他枕頭的氣味  于是我就...
I smelled his pillow, and the next thing I know--
晚安好夢
Okay, night-night.
好了  親愛的  肯定出什么事了
Okay, baby, something definitely isn't right.
快起來  以前我四點才哄你午睡的
Come on. I don't usually put you down for your nap until 4:00.
我第一次在埃蘭家過周末  根本睡不著
I spent my first weekend at Alan's place and couldn't sleep,
因為我怕自己出丑
'cause I was afraid I might do something embarrassing.
沒什么比你醒著的時候做的事更囧的了
It can't be more embarrassing than what you do when you're awake.
我想到一個辦法
Hey, I just got an idea.
你能來我家看我睡覺嗎
Can you come over to my house and watch me sleep?
我也想  但是正在放《驅魔人》
I would, but The Exorcist is on,
美國經典恐怖片
看它都沒看你睡覺嚇人
and watching that sounds a little less scary.
我能幫你弄到亞瑟小子演唱會的前排票
I can get you front-row seats to see Usher!
給我你家地址  鑰匙  備好圣水
I'm gonna need your address, a key, and some holy water.
喬什  我給你做了點點心
Hey, Josh, I made you a little snack--
炸雞配華夫餅
chicken and waffles.
不  謝謝  我不餓
No, thank you. I'm not hungry.
你是問"楓糖漿在哪"嗎
"Where's the maple syrup," you say?
我沒問
I didn't say.
你這話是什么意思
What are you saying?
我是說糖漿在從佛蒙特州
I'm just saying the syrup's on the way over...
來這里的路上
from Vermont.
-你不是吧  -是的
- You didn't. - I did.
我給丹妮爾打了電話  她非常想見她媽媽
I called Danielle, and she really wants to see her mom.
我知道你讓我別這么做  但這是對的
I know you told me not to, but it was the right thing to do.
-我必須這么做  -加比  取消見面
- I had to! - Gabi, call it off.
太晚了
Too late.
肖娜  能下來一下嗎
Shauna, would you come down here, please?
你膽子真大  我明明說了不行
How dare you! I clearly said no.
都沒別的話  就一句"不行"
There were no other words surrounding it. One word. "No."
吵什么呢
What's all the commotion?
肖娜  我希望你明白
Shauna, I want you to know
這件事跟我毫無關系
I had nothing to do with this.
你好  媽媽
Hi, mom.
天吶  丹妮
Oh my God! Dani!
你來這里干什么
What are you doing here?
她飛過整個美國
Well, she flew all the way across the country
就因為她想見你  對嗎  丹妮爾
because she wanted to see you. Isn't that right, Danielle?
加比給我打電話的時候  我就決定來了
When Gabi called me, I jumped at the chance.
你想知道她為什么從不給你寄賀卡嗎
And you wanna know why she never sent you any cards?
你說吧
Well, you tell her.
-因為...  -她非常想要獨立
- It's-- it's-- - She really needed her independence,
但現在她意識到...  你說吧
but now she realizes that-- you tell her.
沒有你的生活一點都不美妙
My life is nowhere near as good without you in it.
你能原諒我嗎
Can you ever forgive me?
我能嗎
Can I?
她能  她能
She can. She can.
喬什 看到沒  跟你說這辦法管用吧
See, Josh? I told you this would all work out.
要是你想幫我報銷她的機票錢
Now, if you wanna pay me back for her plane ticket,
-就再好不過了  -糟了
- that would be really great. - Not cool.
出大事了  這簡直是場災難
This is totally not cool. This is a disaster.
真的嗎  我們看到的是一回事嗎
Seriously? Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
因為我看到的是一幅在我們面前
Because what I'm seeing is a beautiful mother-daughter reunion
母女重聚的溫馨景象
happening right in front of us.
這種情況下會出什么問題啊
What could possibly be wrong with this picture?
她就是摩天輪女孩
That's ferris-wheel girl!
你確定那就是摩天輪女孩嗎
Are you sure that's ferris-wheel girl?
那都是幾年前的漆黑夜晚了
I mean, it was years ago in the dark.
"漆黑"嗎  她整個人都是亮的
Dark? She was all lit up.
她身上一會紅  一會藍
Her body was red, then blue,
一會黃...  然后又變成紅色的了
then yellow... then red again.
或許她不記得你了
Well, maybe she won't remember you.
得了吧  加比  是我哎
Come on, Gabi. It's me!
喬什  我太激動了
Josh, I'm so excited to say this,
認識一下我的女兒丹妮爾
meet my daughter Danielle.
你好  我叫喬什
Hi, I'm Josh.
很高興見到你
Hey, nice to meet you.
我也很高興見到你
Nice to meet you, too.
-這時候該來杯香檳  -好主意
- Well, this calls for champagne. - Great idea!
抱歉  丹妮  是安德森·庫珀打來的
Oh! I'm sorry, Dani. It's Anderson Cooper.
要是不接他會發牢騷  我馬上回來
He gets real whiny if you don't pick up. I'll be right back.
楓糖漿是吧
So... maple syrup, huh?
是的  也是機緣巧合  但挺適合我
Yeah, it's kinda random, but it suits me.
佛蒙特州
Vermont!
那里挺冷的  冬天冰天雪地
Pretty cold there. Gets kind of cold there in the winter.
是啊  冷得沒辦法在摩天輪上嘿咻
Yeah. Way to cold to have sex on a ferris wheel.
我就知道  我知道你記得我
I knew it! I knew you remembered me!
當然  誰忘得了  你一會紅
Yeah, who could forget? You were red,
一會藍  一會黃  然后又變成紅色的了
then blue, then yellow, and then red again.
-香檳來了  -就是她  我說了吧
- Champagne is served. - It's her. I told you.
你是摩天輪女孩嗎
You're ferris-wheel girl?
該死
Damn it!
看看你都做了些什么
Do you see what you did?
你都做了些什么
Do you see what you did
我叫你不要做你非要做的事情
when you did the thing I told you not to do?
要是你沒做你不該做的事情
Well, if you didn't do the thing that you shouldn't have done,
那么我做的這事
then the thing I did
就會變成我該做的了
would've been the thing that I should've done!
我們現在怎么辦
So what are we gonna do?
大家別吵了  好嗎
Okay, everybody just shut up, all right?
今天是個寶貴的日子
This is a very precious day.
你知道你對他做了什么
You know what you did to him.
他知道他對你做了什么  關鍵是
He knows what he did to you. The important thing is
絕不能讓你媽媽知道你們之間做的事
your mother can never find out what you did to each other.
你想讓我欺騙肖娜嗎
You want me to lie to Shauna?
我會很難受的
That puts me in a very uncomfortable position.
是嗎  總不會比你們倆
Oh, really? Well, it can't be any more uncomfortable
在摩天輪上更難受了吧
than the position you guys were in on the ferris wheel!
加比  晚餐太美味了
Gabi, this dinner was absolutely delicious.
而且非常順利
And completely uneventful.
媽媽  你發現
Mom, do you realize
這是三年來我倆第一次共進晚餐嗎
this is the first dinner we've had together in three years?
-為了補償失去的時光  -干杯
- To making up for lost time. - Cheers!
準備好  因為此時此刻
Well, get ready, 'cause now it's time
該是三年來你們倆第一次一起品嘗甜品了
for the first dessert you've had together in three years.
我好高興
I'm so happy.
沒事的  肖娜  我來收拾吧
Oh, don't worry, Shauna. I've got it.
讓我來吧  你為我做的已經太多了
I insist. You've done so much for me.
謝謝
Thanks.
這真是個奇跡
I mean, this is a miracle.
-一切都太順利了  -我知道
- Things are going great. - I know.
-她什么都不知道  -太好了
- She doesn't have a clue. - Well, thank God.
-我真的很喜歡你媽媽  -是啊  她棒極了
- I really like your mom. - Yeah, she's great.
我真的很愛她
I love her... so much,
-還有  你知道嗎  -知道什么
- and you know what? - What?
我也愛你
I love you, too.
自從我們在摩天輪上嘿咻以后
I've thought about you every single night
我每天晚上都在想著你
ever since we made love on that ferris wheel.
那幕一直在我腦海中轉啊轉
It just keeps going round and round in my mind,
-就像...  -就像摩天輪一樣嗎
- like a... - I don't know-- ferris wheel?
沒錯  就是這樣
Yes! That's it!
你太懂我了
You totally get me,
如今我在這里
and now here I am,
坐在你身邊  就像是...
sitting next to you. It's like...
命中注定
destiny!
-誰想去陽臺上吃甜點  -我想  媽媽
- Who's ready for dessert on the terrace? - I am, mommy!
還有  能幫我做點熱巧克力嗎
Oh, and can you make some hot cocoa?
什么都行  親愛的
Anything for you, darling.
她真是陰魂不散
I thought she'd never leave.
你是怎么了  簡直像瘋了一樣
What is wrong with you? You're acting crazy!
不  我沒有
No, I am not.
我只是好想在你脖子上種草莓
I just wanna bite your neck!
-我先出去了  -我也去
- I'll be outside! - We'll be outside!
時間剛剛好  甜品也準備好了
Perfect timing. I've got the dessert.
加比  麻煩大了
Gabi, we have a problem.
-丹妮爾愛上我了  -你怎么會這么想
- Danielle's in love with me. - What? Why would you think that?
她說了"我愛你"  一直愛著我
She said, "I love you," she's never stopped loving me...
-她想在我脖子上種草莓  -我明白了
- She wants to bite my neck. - I see what's going on here.
你只是不高興我不按你說的做
You're just upset because I went against your wishes,
而一切又這么順利  所以你無法接受
it all worked out, and you can't stand it.
加比  給丹妮爾沖熱巧克力的水開了嗎
Gabi, is the water warm yet for Danielle's cocoa?
一切都準備好了
Everything's ready to go.
給你
Here you go.
去吧  快去啊
Go! Go!
你忘了拿棉花糖
Oh, you forgot the marshmallows.
不不不  別走啊
No, no, no, no. Don't go.
你好啊
Hi.
你不能再這樣了
Okay, look, this has to stop.
沒錯  你說得對
You're right. No, you're right.
我是來修復和媽媽的關系的
I came here to fix my relationship with my mother,
所以我們不能這樣
so this can't happen.
-謝謝你  -但這個可以
- Thank you. - But this can.
天啊
Oh god!
真高興能看到你跟丹妮爾重聚
I'm just so happy that you and Danielle are back together!
我也是  但你快把棉花糖擠壞了  親愛的
Me too. You're smushing the marshmallows, darling.
原來你說的不是胸
Oh, the actual marshmallows.
你找到棉花糖了  真棒
Hey, you found the marshmallows. Awesome.
原來已經這么晚了  我得去演播室了
I just noticed the time. I've got to get down to the studio.
我今晚有節目
I'm on air tonight.
-喬什  你會幫我好好招待女兒的對嗎  -不
- Josh, I trust you'll entertain my daughter while I'm out. - No!
我的意思是...  加比
I mean... Gabi?
我在想  既然你要工作
Uh, I was thinking, since you have to work,
或許丹妮爾今晚可以去我那  跟我住
maybe Danielle should come with me and spend the night at my place.
-這主意不錯  -太棒了
- Great idea. - Yes.
不
No!
我只是不想太麻煩你們
I... just don't want to be any trouble.
真的嗎
Really?
沒事的  一點都不麻煩
I mean, yeah, that's no trouble at all.
對啊  你們女生好好去玩玩吧
Yeah, you girls run and have some fun.
見見帥哥什么的  去吧  親愛的
Maybe meet some boys. Come on, darling.
你一直待在佛蒙特那種鄉下地方
You've been stuck in the woods of Vermont.
有多久都沒出去好好瘋狂一番了
When was the last time you went and got crazy?
好了  咱們走
Okay, let's go.
我準備好了  來吧
Okay, let's do this.
老天  你這睡衣是什么做的
Oh my god! How did you make those pajamas?
剝了整間動物園的皮嗎
Did you skin an entire zoo?
我也挺喜歡你的睡衣
I like your pajamas, too.
是跟芭比娃娃一起賣的  還是可以單買
Did it come with Barbie, or was it sold separately?
你睡的是哪張床
Which bed do you sleep in?
那是毛球的床
That's Fluffykins' bed.
他睡得比較晚  要等《法律與秩序》播完以后
He turns in late, after Law & Order.
你在做什么  我要你睡到床上來
What are you doing? I need you in the bed,
這樣我才能假裝有人睡在我身邊
so I can simulate having a person next to me while I sleep.
我才不要跟你假裝什么
I'm not simulating anything!
知道嗎  老娘不干了
You know what? Forget this whole thing.
我給你弄到了亞瑟小子的票  我們說好了的
I got you tickets to Usher. We had a deal!
好吧  那我要用枕頭堆座墻
Fine! But I'm building a pillow wall.
跟一個男人同床共枕卻不能碰
Getting into bed with a man and not touching him.
就跟老娘當年結婚時一模一樣
It's like I'm married all over again.
她在狂親她老媽的男朋友
She was kissing all over her mother's boyfriend?
我在浪漫肥皂劇里看過這橋段
Ooh! I saw this on a telenovela once.
她是剛剛從昏迷中蘇醒嗎
Did she just come out of a coma?
小聲點  我不想讓她聽見
I don't want her to hear.
別擔心  她在洗澡呢
Don't worry about it. She's in the shower.
回來的這一路上
I mean, the whole way over here
我都在勸她  如果她要勾引喬什
I was trying to convince her that if she went for Josh,
就會徹底毀了她跟她老媽的關系
then she would ruin her relationship with her mother forever.
你知道她說什么嗎
And you know what she said?
"喬什嘗起來像棉花糖"
"Josh tastes like cotton candy!"
她還得在這待兩天呢
I mean, she's here for two more days.
-我該怎么辦  -不  你沒時間了
- What am I gonna do? - Oh, no, no, you don't have two more days.
這瘋女人隨時都會爆發  你得趕緊弄走她
That crazy bomb is ticking. You need to get rid of her now.
或者  我可以
Or-- I mean, what if I pull out
把我和媽媽的相冊拿給她看
all the photo albums of me and my mother, I mean,
讓她明白什么是真正的母女關系
and show her what a real relationship looks like?
我覺得這是我媽媽會想讓我做的
I feel like that's what my mom's telling me to do.
真的嗎  你再好好聽聽
Really? Listen again.
因為我覺得她說的是
Because what I'm hearing is...
"趕緊把那瘋婆子送去機場
"Drive that crazy bitch to the airport
讓她坐飛機回佛蒙特去"
"and put her on a plane to Vermont."
知道嗎  我還是去把相冊拿出來
You know what? I think I'm gonna get out the photo albums,
這樣等她洗完澡出來
so when she gets out of the shower,
-就可以...  -等等
- then she's-- - Wait, wait, wait, wait.
她在里面待了好久
She's been in there for forever.
熱水應該二十分鐘前就用光了
She should've run out of hot water 20 minutes ago.
天吶
Oh god!
天吶  天吶  天吶
Oh god! Oh god! Oh god!
或許你說的沒錯
Maybe my mom really was talking to you,
那瘋婆子居然從浴室窗戶里爬出去了
because that crazy bitch climbed out the bathroom window!
就跟浪漫肥皂劇里一樣
Just like the telenovela.
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no!
不
No! No!
不不不不不
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
丹妮爾  停下
Danielle, stop!
就算你和喬什以前在摩天輪上嘿咻過
Just because you once had sex with Josh on a ferris wheel,
也不代表你現在能偷偷爬上他床啊
doesn't mean you can sneak into be with him now!
我可以解釋
I can explain.
我讓你不要把肖娜女兒接過來
I asked you not to fly Shauna's daughter out here,
但你接了
but you did.
本來沒人會告訴肖娜
And no one was supposed to tell Shauna
我和她女兒上過床
that I had sex with her daughter,
但你說了
but you did.
或許會沒事的呢
Maybe it's gonna be okay.
在度過最初的震驚期之后
I mean, after she gets over her initial shock,
肖娜會沒事的
Shauna's gonna be fine.
喬什  和你一起的這兩周真的很愉快
Josh, these two weeks have been some of the best times I've ever had,
我真是沒想到結局會是這么羞辱  再見
and I never imagined it would come to such a humiliating end. Goodbye!
肖娜  等等
Shauna, wait.
我們都有過去
Look... we all have pasts.
重要的是我想和你在一起
The important thing is I wanna be with you.
不  你睡了我女兒
No, you had sex with my daughter!
你們美國人怎么說的來著
What's that thing all the Americans say?
對了  惡心
Oh yeah. Eww!
是丹妮爾的短信
Oh, it's Danielle.
"媽媽  楓糖廠出了急事  得回家了
"Mom, maple syrup emergency. Had to fly home.
見到你和喬什在一起真高興
So thrilled about you and Josh, and...
喜歡看你幸福的樣子  親親抱抱  丹妮爾"
I loved seeing you so happy. Kiss, hug, Danielle."
看到了嗎  你和喬什她選了你
See? See? She chose you over Josh.
我做的很對
I did the right thing.
雖然可笑  但沒錯
I guess, in a funny way, you did.
再見  加比
Goodbye, Gabi.
再見  喬什
Goodbye, Josh.
我只抱沒睡過我女兒的人
Hugs are for people who haven't slept with my daughter.
為什么
Why?
為什么  為什么
Why? Why?
為什么
Why? Why? Why?
為什么  為什么  為什么
Why? Why, why, why? Why?
為什么  你猜怎么著  不用回答
Why? You know what? Don't answer that question!
請你出去
Get out!
出去
Out!
埃蘭  我想說"太陽曬屁股了"
Alan, I would say, "Rise and shine,"
可在我屁股上的不是太陽嘛
but it appears somebody already has.
我不是埃蘭
I'm not Alan,
那是我的發卷
and that's one of my hair rollers!
尤蘭達
Yolanda!
你該看著我睡覺的
You were supposed to be watching me,
不是沾我一身女人臭味
not getting your woman stink on me.
對不起  我就閉了一下眼
I'm sorry! I closed my eyes for one second,
美國演員  身高僅152
然后就發現摟著亞洲版的丹尼·德維托醒來了
next thing I know, I woke up spooning an Asian Danny DeVito!
等等  所以你整晚都睡過去了嗎
Wait, so you slept the whole night?
沒看我干了什么嗎
You didn't see me do anything?
放心  我們晚上都在睡覺
Oh, relax! We both slept through the night.
能發生什么奇怪的事
What's the weirdest thing that could've happened?
等等  你怎么會...
Wait. How did you get my--
你又怎么穿了...
And how did you manage to put on...
你怎么會來  一定不是好事
Why are you here? It can't be good.
加比  開門
Gabi, open the door.
首先  我要跟你說我真的對這一切
Okay, first, let me start by saying I'm really, really sorry
很抱歉  為了補償你
about everything, and to make it up to you,
我做了你最喜歡的菜
I made your favorite dish.
-松露奶酪通心粉嗎  -你第二喜歡的
- Truffle mac and cheese? - Your second favorite dish.
索菲亞打電話給我  我知道這周是你媽媽的生日
Sofia called me, and I know it was your mother's birthday this week.
這也就解釋了你昨天的行為
And I think that explains your behavior yesterday.
但不包括其他天的
Not every other day.
我猜每年的這個時候我都很難受
I guess this time of year's really hard for me.
如果你想聊聊  我的門永遠對你敞開
I want you to know my door's always open if you need to talk.
不是臥室門
Not my bedroom door.
在你說了那么多"為什么"以后
I guess after you said, "Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?",
讓我也開始思考  為什么呢
it really made me think, "Why?"
然后我明白了我只是
And I realized I was just trying
想從丹妮爾和肖娜身上產生共鳴
to live vicariously through Danielle and Shauna.
覺得如果我能讓她倆團聚  那...
I thought maybe if I could get them back together, then...
天啊  能再和媽媽團聚我干什么都可以
God, I would do anything to have one more moment with my mom.
我知道
I know...
所以這周剩下的時間我給你放假
which is why I'm giving you the rest of the week off
送你和索菲亞去玩一趟
and sending you and Sofia on a little trip.
什么  去哪里
What? Where are we going?
讓我給你個小提示
Let me... give you a little hint.
史密森尼博物館的茱莉亞·蔡爾德烹飪展嗎
Julia Child's kitchen in the Smithsonian?
-媽媽一直想帶我去的  -我知道
- My mom always wanted to take me here. - I know.
索菲亞已經幫你收好了行李  她在機場等我們
Sofia already packed your bags. She's meeting us at the airport.
等等  我毀了你的戀愛
Wait, wait, wait. I ruined your relationship,
你還要讓我免費旅游嗎
and you're sending me on a free trip?
我不該提這茬的
I should not have mentioned that.
至少讓我給你為你做的芝士煎雞排
At least let me give you the chicken parm that I made you.
芝士雞排  前十都不是好嗎
Chicken parm? Not even top 10.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
還有件事
One more thing.
謝謝
Thank you.
艾略特  我有話要跟你說
Elliot, I have something to tell you.
-什么  -我在你身邊睡不著
- What? - I've been having a hard time sleeping next to you.
好擔心睡夢中會做什么事
I'm so worried that I might do something in my sleep
讓你覺得我不性感了
and you won't think I'm sexy anymore.
-什么  -我知道
- What? - I know.
我這么玉樹臨風  怎么可能
With this moneymaker, that's crazy.
但萬一呢
But what if?
你在擔心這個嗎
You've been worried about that?
我擔心的也是這個
I've been worried about the same thing!
拜托  你有什么好擔心的
Oh please. You don't know from worry.
我當然有  我擔心到
I don't? I was so worried,
花錢讓尤蘭達看我睡覺
I paid Yolanda to watch me sleep.
你太貼心了
That's so sweet!
-你們做了什么奇怪的事嗎  -沒有
- Did you do anything weird? - No.
真是瘋狂  誰在意我們怎么睡覺呢
This is crazy. Who cares what we do in our sleep?
我們可以做自己  我們那么相愛
We can be ourselves. We love each other.
-有嗎  -我是的
- We do? - Well... I do.
我也是
I do too.
那就好  因為我有睡眠呼吸暫停癥
Good, because I have sleep apnea.
晚安  親愛的
Good night, sweetheart.
管它呢
Oh, who cares?